stephon@stephonautery.com

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Employment in a dynamic environment where I can use my years of technology experience to advance business goals. I have development experience using Agile Software Development methodologies, tools and workflows to specify, purchase, configure, manage and secure technology in mid-sized and large production environments.

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

CSS, HTML, JavaScript, ASP, React/Redux/Hooks, C++, Python, Node.js, NPM, MongoDB, Mongoose, Transact-SQL, NoSQL, Veeva CLM, Adobe Creative Cloud Suite, Git.

### SALARY REQUIRMENTS

Flexible.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2007 - 2019

### Autery Household, San Leandro, CA Homemaker

- Primary Caregiver and Household Manager: Planned meals, scheduled activities, managed healthecare issues and coordinated activities among all members of a family of four, 3 dogs and 12 chickens while my Wife traveled 35% 40% of the year and worked 50 60 hours a week as part of her job duties.
- Early Childhood Education: Taught both our children to read and write at 3 years old.
- Household Upgrades: Completed daily household maintenance and a complete
  overhaul and upgrade of the garden and irrigation, plumbing, and electrical systems in a
  99 year old Craftsman style home with documented compliance to city code
  requirements.
- Swim Team: Volunteer Snack Shop Back of House (BOH) Manager for four years. Managed all BOH operations, coordinating with the Kitchen Manager to organize up to 6 BOH volunteers per meet over the course of a 12 meet season. Specified and purchased and prepared all food, supplies and sundries to run 2 grills and 2 cook stations to serve hot breakfast sandwhiches and tacos on-site during meets resulting in average profits of up to \$900.00 per meet.

Nominated for Swim Team Board of Directors 3 years in a row.

#### 2003 - 2017

### **Green Street Media**, San Leandro, CA **Principal**

Developed web applications integrating HTML, CSS, ASP, C++, JavaScript and Transact-SQL and the enire Adobe Creative Cloud suite of products for a diverse client base. Developed print, videography and multimedia campaigns for local non-profits. Rapidly developed film projects for screening at International Film Festivals and SAG (Screen Actor's Guild) productions.

#### • Measure LL - Video Campaign

Created a series of Campaign Ads in support of the Coalition for Police Accountability. The measure would establish a Police Commission ("Commission") to oversee the Police Department's policies and procedures, and a Community Police Review Agency ("Agency") to investigate complaints of police misconduct and recommend discipline. Ads ran on local TV stations and in on-line outreach campaigns. Measure LL passed with 80% of the vote.

http://www.stephonautery.com/truth/truth.asp

#### UnCommon Law: Homecoming – Event Videography and Print Campaign

Designed and supervised the production of a print media campaign for the organizations UnCommon Law: UnCommon Homecoming event to raise money for the operation of the UnCommon Law organization.

http://stephonautery.com/UnCommon/posters.asp

Acted as Producer, Lead Videographer and Director of the UnCommon Law: UnCommon Homecoming event.

The campaign raised almost half a million dollars and was the most succesful fundraising campaign in the organizations history.

http://stephonautery.com/truth/truth.asp

### • 2017 - Are You Safe - 48 Hour Film Festival

Recruited and supervised a 12 person crew of actors and artists to write, produce and edit a short film in 48 hours. Acted as Co-Writer, Producer and Director on the project. http://www.stephonautery.com/fiction/fiction.asp

Project completed on time and screened at the festival opening to positive reviews.

#### 2014 – I Miss You When You're Gone - 48 Hour Film Festival

Recruited and supervised a 14 person crew of actors and artists to write, produce, and edit a short film in 48 hours. Acted as Co-Writer, Producer and Director on the project. <a href="http://www.stephonautery.com/fiction/fiction.asp">http://www.stephonautery.com/fiction/fiction.asp</a>

Project was completed on time and screened at the festival opening to positive reviews.

### • Desiree Café – In the Presidio – Full Stack Website Development

Used HTML, CSS, ASP, C++, JavaScript and SQL server to developed an intertactive web application incoroporating a menu management system for the restaurents staff and a public facing ordering system resulting in a 35% increase in on-site sales, a 10% increase in food sales in the larger San Francisco bay area and a 22% increase in event bookings throughout California.

http://stephonautery.com/work/desiree cafe/default.asp

#### 2000 - 2002

## **Channel Advisor Corporation**, Morrisville, NC **Director Information Systems**

- Configured, installed and maintained 98 server class computers, 80 workstations and other peripheral assets including hubs, switches, routers, load balancers, firewalls and assorted business technology across 2 sites and 3 computing environments.
- Managed assets valued in excess of 10 million dollars, including 5 corporate servers, 42 staging servers and 51 production servers in a co-located server farm and provided 24/7/365 support of production and corporate facilities and personell.
- Maintained 99.89% overall uptime during my employment as Director Information Systems resulting in Channel Advisor Corporation being recognized as an industry leader in service availability.
- Configured and managed Microsoft Windows Advance Server, Cluster Server, Windows NT, SQL Server, Microsoft Internet Information Server, and Microsoft Exchange Server in a co-located, mixed-mode server farm resulting in a marked increase in reliability, scalability and availability.
- Supervised the migration of all technical operations from Windows NT, SQL Server, Microsoft Exchange Server and IIS to Windows Advanced Server, Windows Cluster Server, SQL Server, Microsoft Exchange Server and IIS.
- Installed, configured and managed Microsoft Exhcange Server and connected Corporate MSExchange Server accross Point to Point ISDN to production site utilizing Multiple information Stores, Site Connectors, Internet Mail Services and Outlook Web Access. Implemented company wide collaboration tools utilizing Public Information Stores and Microsoft Outlook.

- Relocated co-located production assets valued in excess of 7.5 million dollars to new
  co-location production facilities. Project completed 3 weeks ahead of schedule, utilizing
  less than 60% of allocated funds with less than 12 hours of down-time on production
  site.
- Selected vendors, specified equipment and executed all corporate technology purchases while staying within budgetary constraints resulting in significant savings to Channel Advisor Corporation.
- Hired and managed a 4 person team-oriented Information Technology (IT) staff to monitor, maintain and efficiently manage all aspects of Channel Advisor technical operations on a 24 hour basis resulting in increased customer satisfaction and a 23% increase in sytem-wide availability.

#### 1998 - 2000

# **North Carolina Administrative Services Organization**, Durham, NC **Director Information Systems**

- Planned, installed and maintained enterprise-wide LAN/WAN and all aspects of network file servers and all telecom/PBX equipment, including Nortel Meridian phone switches.
- Specified, acquired, configured and implemented all Internet/WAN technology including all routers, switches and hubs, installed all premise wiring (EIA/TIA 568B) resulting in substantial cost savings.
- Installed, configured and managed Microsoft Exhcange Server. Connected MSExchange Server accross Point to Point ISDN to several sites utilizing Multiple information Stores, Site Connectors, Internet Mail Services and Outlook Web Access. Implemented company wide collaboration tools utilizing Public Information Stores.
- Specified approximately \$1,250,000.00 in organizational technology purchases.
- Designed, implemented and managed all aspects of corporate World Wide Web presence, database development and vendor selection resulting in a 40% increase in organization membership.

#### 1996 - 1998

# **International Heritage Inc.,** Raleigh, NC **Manager of Information Systems**

- Improved corporate comminications across internationally dispersed sites by planning, installing, and maintaining all enterprise LAN/WAN equipment consisting of 3 Cisco 2500 routers, 5 Cisco 1600 routers, and 2 Ascend P75 routers resulting in minimized down time and improved customer satisfaction.
- Installed, configured and managed multi-site corporate-wide Microsoft Exhcange Server. Connected MSExchange Servers across Point to Point ISDN to several sites in the US and Canada utilizing Multiple information Stores, Site Connectors and the Internet Mail Service. Implemented company wide collaboration tools utilizing Public Information Stores.
- Managed all server hardware and operating systems including 6 Compaq Prosignia class servers running Windows NT 4.0, 1 Hewlett Packard 9000 series K220 running HP/UX v10.20, 1 HP NetServer LM running SCO UNIX.
- Configured and managed legacy telecom/PBX equipment, including 2 ADIX-M phone switches, acquired and implemented updated 1250 user telecom/PBX equipment.

#### 1994 - 1996

# **Duke University Department of Neurobiology,** Durham, NC **Network Systems Analyst**

- Planned, installed and managed departmental Novell Netware, 2 Windows NT file-servers, UNIX mail-server, Ethernet/Appletalk LAN/WAN.
- Installed, maintained and supported 350 workstations and users.
- Specified approximately \$350,000.00 in departmental technology purchases on a yearly basis.

1985 – 1992 United States Marine Corps, Camp LeJeune, NC Infantry Officer, 2<sup>nd</sup> Marines, 2<sup>nd</sup> Battalion

• Led, disciplined, administered, motivated and counseled United States Marines while completing mission objectives.

#### **EDUCATION**

2021 UC Berkeley Extension

**Certificate – Full Stack Developer** 

1984 - 1991 North Carolina State University

B.S. Mechanical Engineering, Raleigh, NC

• Completed degree requirements while working full time and serving in the United States Marine Corps.

### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Father of 2 awesome kids, sewist, musician and animal lover. I have raised 2 children and I knit and sew clothing for them as well as playing guitar and Mandolin. I have assisted in the care, fostering and placement of 62 puppies or homeless dogs, and raised over \$9,500.00 for Leukemia & Lymphoma cancer research.